So what should our next project be?
Why don't we start by researching the latest crazes?
Sounds good.
Mickey Nikaidou in Japan?
This just in.
Mickey Nikaidou, one of the Designers Seven
and creator of the brand Universe Queen,
appears to have entered Japan incognito.
Unfortunately, due to the lack of an official statement,
we have to rely on hearsay...
You can't see his face at all.
Is he really one of the Designers Seven?
Universe Queen, eh?
People love it for combining
an ostentatious look with a touch of funk.
It's renowned for being showy and gorgeous.
He does seem to suit the brand's image...
No fooling.
But that'd be pretty cool, wouldn't it?
Mickey Nikaidou in Japan?
It is unclear what business he might have in Japan,
but sources say another Special Tournament may be planned in the near future.
People say the man himself loves being showy as well.
Appearing and disappearing
without warning is just his style.
I get it! And making a stir
lets him promote his brand too.
Mickey Nikaidou in Japan?
However, there has been no word on Mickey
since he was sighted at the airport.
Mickey Nikaidou in Japan?
His plans are currently unknown.
We will keep you updated as we learn more.
In other news...
Do you think they'll do another Special Tournament?
This time we'll have Rinka on stage with us.
Miracle Kiratts is gonna win again for sure!
You think so?
Hold on, we have our next show to concentrate on first.
Working hard, girls?
Have some snacks.
Woo-hoo! Time for a break!
But we haven't done anything yet.
We need sugar if we're gonna be using our brains.
Emo-chan...
Well, a breather might help the creative juices flow.
Good point.
And we shouldn't let these go to waste.
Awright!
What?
Poke, poke.
Wow!
It's alive!
Now it's time to start: sprinkle a little excitement
hajimeyou wakuwaku wo furimaite
I'm gonna make a channel
watashi iro no channeru
In my own colour
tsukucchaou
Throw together an outfit from my special faves
oki ni iri totteoki no koode shite
We'll wear our happy smiles
genki na sumairu
And strut our stuff
apiiru shiyou
The thought of being in the limelight gets my heart racing
ninkimono ni naritai tokimeki
Though I've always tried to keep it to myself
itsumo kakushiteita no
If you all follow me, there'll be nothing I can't do
minna no foroo ga areba muteki
So let's spread our wings
dakara habatakou
The twinkling chance we long for is sparkling
kiratto akogare kirakira kanaeru chansu da yo
Pri☆Chan's a place where dreams come to life
yume wo sakaserareru purichan
Linking hands and spreading happiness across the world
sekaijuu wo happii de tsunageyou
It'll be more fabulous than any magic
mahou yori suteki na
So come on – the show's about to start!
raibu ga hajimaru yo
Mel Tried Becoming a Detective!
So what d'ya want with us?
An-An and Sarara are busy as beavers with an event.
So I thought, "I bet Kiratts are free as birds."
Hey – we were busy with a meeting!
Oh, my humble apologies.
So by the way, who might this person be?
The mysterious Mr. Fainted Person!
Hello there.
Mr. Fainted Person?
He was lying all flat over by
the road there, but he revived.
So he's Mr. Fainted Person.
I remember I met you fainted
by the road not too long ago.
Me too! Thanking you kindly once again!
So what happened to him, exactly?
Well...
He's got no memories! Zilch!
I have no recollection of why I'm here.
I can't even remember my own name.
Then does he have amnesia?
Yes!
That's why I'm on the hunt for the memories he lost!
Losing your memories isn't like losing your keys...
Do you have any idea where to look?
I have me a clue!
How's your PriCast supposed to be a clue?
What, you don't get it?
Of course I don't!
Um...
I have a feeling I've seen that PriCast thing before.
Maybe he used to stream on Pri☆Chan?
Or he could have worked
at a Prism Stone shop somewhere.
Maybe we could ask Meganee-san
if she knows anything.
Right, right!
Yes, yes!
If he used to stream videos,
we might be able to find them on the net.
That's why I'm going to use this
to look for Mr. Fainted Person's memories!
Aha!
So you invited us to give you a hand?
You got it!
No, no!
Huh?
This is what I need a hand with!
I took Mr. Fainted Person to this café to talk,
so I ordered lots of scrumptious food.
But I left my wallet at home!
So couldja handle the bill? Please and thankies!
Hey, Mel-chan!
Get back here!
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
I'll pay you back later!
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Item
Pudding
Strawberry Parfait
Mont
Look, Anna.
Mickey Nikaidou in Japan?
It seems there's going to be another Special Tournament.
Kiratts managed to slip ahead a little last time.
But now that we're three,
Meltic StAr has attained perfection!
Victory is certain!
Right you are.
Hello there, young ladies.
May I have a moment of your time?
And who might you be?
Say, that hairstyle...
Excuse me.
Are you, perhaps...
The very same!
I am Mickey Nikaidou!
One of the Designers Seven –
I knew I recognised you!
I'm simply honoured to meet you!
What brings you here?
People are talking about
how you disappeared in the airport.
It's just so stifling with the media
hounding you everywhere you go.
And of course, I couldn't get in touch
with the most popular Pri☆Chan idols!
The most popular Pri☆Chan idols?
How graciously honest of you.
So what business do you have with us?
I'm in search of Pri☆Chan idols fit to wear my brand!
Which is to say...
Indeed!
I wish to become the producer for Meltic StAr!
If you'd have me!
My, what excellent taste you have!
Don't get carried away, Anna.
Oh, come now, Sara, this is the best news
that could possibly follow Meltic StAr's revival!
Now, there's a lot I'd like to discuss.
The events, for example.
And, of course, the matter of accompanying expenses...
But of course!
A grand event to celebrate
Meltic StAr's rise to perfection –
we shan't spare any expense!
Let us begin!
We can discuss all the details at my residence.
Let us make haste!
Goodness gracious.
How exciting this all is!
To think one of the world-renowned Designers Seven
would wish to be our producer!
What a trusting little girl.
It'll be easier than I thought
to milk her for her money's worth.
Don't worry about a thing! Leave it all to me!
I certainly shall!
First, let's return to the scene of the incident.
This is where you were flat out fainted, yes?
Right.
And this PriCast is our clue!
So now what do we do?
First, the basics of investigation.
We'll gather all possible information!
Oh, hello there! Do you know this person?
No.
That right?
Hey there! Do you know who this person is?
Uh, can't say I recognise him.
I see. You too, huh?
That's a pity.
But we'll keep trying. Never give up!
Bring on the next person!
Excuse me, I want to ask you something.
Do you kids know this person?
Nope!
Does anyone know him?
Hey, hey!
In that case...
Why don't you try asking on Pri☆Chan?
Eureka!
That's all my pocket money for the month.
I sure hope Mel comes to pay us back.
I'm sure she will, Emo-chan.
Mel-chan's streaming?
Is this working?
Hello! Am I live, everyone?
No problem?
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
You're on camera!
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
You're on camera!
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What's going on?
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Okay! Let's get started.
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Nice and clear!
It's Mel-Mel!
What a cute outfit
What's going on?
You're on camera!
What's happening?
Hello ♪
Hype
Solving a
MYSTERY!
I'm gathering intel!
Solving a
MYSTERY!
I wanna know...
Solving a
MYSTERY!
Who is this guy?
Who is this
person?
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
He's out of frame.
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
What's happening?
Can't see
He's out of frame
What are you doing?
We can't tell anything
He's not visible
Show him properly
Pan up!
Don't know him
Who is this
person?
Show him properly!
We can't tell anything.
Who is this
person?
Send me your intelligence!
For us, it's recon time – let's search!
Go, go!
I don't get this show one bit.
This is just a mess.
Hello!
Do you know this person?
We think this PriCast is a clue.
Hey, you! Didn't your mummies teach you
to listen when people speak to you?
Um...
The cats in this area seem to avoid humans.
But have no fear!
Detective Mel is on the case!
Hey, hey! Do you know this person?
Not a word passes his lips.
Onwards, undaunted!
To the next challenge!
Do you know him?
Not a single person had the intel we needed.
To be fair, you didn't exactly ask many people.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
This way, please.
One of the Designers Seven, eh?
I can't wait to hear your plans for our career.
W-Well, it will come down to your own talent.
First, let me see your singing and dancing skills.
If – and only if – you satisfy me,
we can draw up a proper contract.
Very well!
Please allow us a minute to prepare.
Let us go.
Man, this whole place stinks of money –
you can't bloody relax.
Let's check what's stashed away
in case I need to do a bunk.
Blimey.
If I tried making off with this junk,
they'd pin it on me straight away.
M-My, what a marvellous collection you have!
I think I'll go and get some fresh air!
I'll be right back.
Hey Anna, do you really think
he's one of the Designers Seven?
Who else could he be?
You say the broadcast with the member
of the Designers Seven at the airport just as I did.
Well, we didn't see his face.
Who but one of the Designers Seven
would have such an idiosyncratic hairstyle?
Mel has returned to us,
and now one of the Designers Seven
will be the producer for the perfect,
newly-revived Meltic StAr!
We must seize an opportunity so overflowing
in celebrity and gorgeous appeal as this!
I guess not.
Well, if you're sure.
I'll do as you say.
Thank you for your patience!
Shall we begin?
What did you think of our abilities?
We're one girl down,
but we'll only be more magnificent with her as well.
I'm more than convinced of your abilities.
I shall be your producer!
Now then, there will be much to organise...
If you mean funding...
Will this suffice?
I think that'll do quite nicely!
Regrettably, the only cash I can offer
at the moment is my own pocket money.
Do accept this pure gold statue of me too.
If that's insufficient, we can...
N-No, this is quite enough.
In that case, we shall make an official announcement!
Mickey Nikaidou has signed on
as Meltic StAr's producer –
we must share this momentous news!
What, right now?
There's no sense wasting time!
Meltic StAr
Huge Announcement
The stadium is already prepared!
Meltic StAr
Huge Announcement
The what now?!
Let us be off!
I can't find any clues at all.
I'm sorry for all this trouble.
No worries! Not a problem!
It's ok-ok-okay! Oll korrect!
I wonder who on earth I am.
Strangely familiar.
Hum... de dum...
Hum-de-dum-dum-dum.
Yes, I know you from somewhere.
What?
An-An?
Meltic StAr
Huge Announcement
Meltic StAr Emergency Conference
A Meltic StAr Emergency Conference?
An-An knows a bunch of people! Let's ask her!
An-An?
What's that now?
You don't know An-An?
Crud! How did I get into this mess?
I thought I could put one over
on this rich kid and it'd be smooth sailing.
I'm trapped like a rat.
Is Mel still not answering?
I keep messaging her PriCast,
but she's not coming online.
She always has to make things difficult, doesn't she?
I-In that case, hadn't we better postpone
until all three of you are here?
Let's do that!
Oh, heavens no – who knows when she'll decide to turn up!
We should simply get things underway.
Come, let us be on our way!
What's going on now?
Mickey Nikaidou's supposed to be in Japan...
Do you think that's related?
Meltic StAr's been busy lately.
This could be a scoop!
We greatly appreciate you attending Meltic StAr's
emergency conference on such short notice.
Thank you very much!
Now, to elaborate on today's purpose:
our newly-completed team
is about to advance another step...
I'm in for it now!
They'll figure out I'm a phony any second!
Hey, isn't that Mickey Nikaidou?
I'm sunk!
Look at that hairstyle – there's no doubt about it!
That's him, all right!
This must be what he came to Japan for.
They didn't figure it out yet!
I've come all this way tricking that rich kid.
No turning back now – you'll never know if you don't try!
Whoever's calling me now?
Mel! Where are you?
Right here!
Mel-Mel's in the house!
Mel-chan?!
Look out!
Wh-What in heavens is going on?
Hey there, are you okay?
I'm...
That's right!
I recall now.
I recall the person –
no, the man I am!
Fever!
Thanks for waiting!
Mickey Nikaidou's back, baby!
It's the person who had amnesia!
He was one of the Designers Seven?
Yes, of course! Elementary!
I expect you're all dying to know why I'm here.
But now is not the time!
However, I have something even cooler
to show you, so make some noise!
All I can say for now is that we're hoping
to get lots of Pri☆Chan idols on board!
Looks like we've got enough likes.
I reckon it's time for Meltic StAr to wrap this party up!
Hooray! Time for a show!
Wh-What's happening now?
Come on, Anna, look at all the size of this crowd.
We can't let them go without a song and dance.
Yes! Let's get this show on the road!
Sara! Mel! Wait a moment!
I don't understand what's going on one bit!
Dance "gave it a try app": set!
PriTicket: swipe!
My unbeatable and perfect Pri☆Chan's live on the air!
Cutely!
Clean...
Check it out!
It's a super cool Mel-Mel outfit!
You may gaze upon my lovely raiment!
Sharp!
Here it is: my impeccably cool outfit!
We're Meltic StAr.
Today's outfit is the Punk Cat Ensemble.
It's got a rock style with leather and chains.
Now Meltic StAr's concert...
Is starting!
You see!
When you start yearning for radiance
kagayaki wa akogareta shunkan
It seems so far away
doushite ka tookunacchau kedo
(Longing for, longing for, longing for – chu chu la!)
(longing for longing for longing for chu chu la)
(Longing for, longing for, longing for that star)
(longing for longing for longing for star)
The glimmer passing right by
me no mae wo toorisugita shining
Whips up a solar flare in my heart
kizuitara okotteru my big bang
(Longing for, longing for, longing for that star)
(longing for longing for longing for star)
And it's dancing, sparkling in the sky
ima kiratto sora ni odoru
(Like a twinkling star)
(hoshi mitai ni)
This miracle eclipses all else in our minds
hitosuji no kiseki sagase
(This song's taking off!)
(up and shooting song)
(This dance is taking off!)
(up and shooting dance)
(This show's leaving the Earth!)
(up and shooting this stage)
This cometic silhouette showers us with happiness
cometic shiruetto furase shiawase
As we dance in the hall of all the cosmos
uchuu datte dansuhooru
Mixing our lovely, cool and poppy styles together
lovely coolish poppu wo mazekoze
One, two, and...
I gave it a try!
We'll see the dawn of a new world
atarashii sekai
This cometic silhouette showers you with happiness
cometic shiruetto furase shiawase
Let's party!
All the cosmos is a hall for us to dance
uchuu datte dansuhooru
A shooting star that never falls!
Anna!
With the brilliance of this one unique star
onriiwan na hoshi wo kirameki
Mel!
Sarara!
I like it!
We'll see a brand new world
atarashii sekai
Sweet Sweet Dancing Queen!
This cometic silhouette holds the thread of all your dreams
cometic shiruetto souzou no shippo wa
Stretching forth into infinity
mugendai ni nobiteku yo
And you raise your eyes to see
miageta kimi no hitomi ni
This Meltic StAr for you!
todoku meltic star
This Meltic StAr shines true!
hikaru meltic star
Look...
A sparkling button!
A destined moment: Sparkling Chance!
Go!
Wow!
The Designers Seven...
And a twinkling mirror ball!
The sparkling chance is twinkling
kiratto chansu wo kirakira
Sparkling Chance, switch on!
Embrace it with arms spread wide
ryoute de dakishimeyou
Shiny!
The Sparkling Ensemble's glittering!
Press the button of destiny
unmei no botan wo oshite
The Sparkling Ensemble's complete!
Take this brand-new miracle in your hands
mita koto no nai mirakuru getto shiyou
It'll be more fabulous than any magic
mahou yori suteki na
So come on – the show's about to start!
raibu ga hajimaru yo
Sparkling Roulette!
Go...
KiraTicket!
Thanks for the help.
I didn't recognise you
without your hairstyle at all, Mickey!
Everyone remembers the 'do.
They all love it, baby!
No comment.
What does this mean?
Are there two Mickey Nikaidous?
No, no, Anna.
The one who said he'd be our producer
was a complete phony.
A ph-phony?
So then this fellow is the real one?
I'm a bit worried it took you this long to put it together.
By the way, how did you get amnesia?
You see...
When I was planning my surprise,
some feathered friends attacked my 'do.
I lost my balance and knocked myself out cold.
What a flock of troublemakers.
Now then, I'm back off to work.
Keep up the hard work, ladies.
Bye-bye!
By the way, Mel, how do you know Mickey Nikaidou?
I ran into him in the ol' US of A.
How on earth did you just "run into"
one of the Designers Seven?
Well...
I'm hungry.
Simply starved.
Then how about we grab some doughnuts
and you can regale us with tales of your travels?
Doughnuts!
Yes, yes! Take me to the doughnuts!
Now just a moment! Just a moment, I say!
Yay! Doughnut time!
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Pri☆Chan!
chanchan puu chanchan puu purichan
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, time to begin!
chanchan puu chanchan puu hajimaru
Sending max excitement through the screen
sukurin goshi dokidoki makkusu
Shining like crazy! It's like a jewel!
kirameki ippai houseki mitai
Laughter and tears and happiness and everything else
warai naki yorokobi nandemo
This magic sends it all to you!
tsutaeteikeru mahou da yo
Come on, don't you want to try it too?
hora kimi mo mezashitai desho
Com on, then, I'll show you!
sore nara oshiete ageru ne
Just put a bit of courage in your pocket
yuuki chotto poochi ni iretara
Here we go, time for Pri☆Chan!
ima sugu purichan
No rivals here
raibaru nante inai
We're dreamers, one and all
yume miru hito wa minna
It's so cute! I love it a bunch!
kawaii ne meccha suki
Let's be friends!
let's be friends
On this channel of dreams, we can all be
yume e no channeru de dare mo ga minna
Gleaming, gleaming, glee
pikkan pikkan pii
Yes, you and me as well
ima sugu hora kimi mo boku mo
Let's be cute kitty idols
nyawa aidoru desu
Give it a tap, give it a swipe
pikon tappu tappu chotto suwaipu
Gleaming, gleaming, glee
pikkan pikkan pii
And send all your love out
okki na ai sekaijuu ni
Across the whole world
todokete ne
All together!
issho ni
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Pri☆Chan!
chanchan puu chanchan puu purichan
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan☆Pri? Wait, that's wrong!
chanchan puu chanchan puu chanpuri chigau
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Pri☆Chan!
chanchan puu chanchan puu purichan
Check it out! It's time to begin!
mite mite hajimaru
Next Time
I'm Devi!
Ride the teacups
10 times.
And I'm Luu!
And together...
We're Li'l Lady Tricks!
What? You're real lazy?
No!
We're not lazy – we're Li'l Lady Tricks!
Oh my gosh! New rivals have appeared!
And they're called Real Lazy Tricks!
Li'l Lady Tricks!
Next time: We Tried Playing Pranks with Lollies!
Join hands and expand our follower world!
We Tried Playing Pranks with Lollies!
Our fabulous show's live on the air!