KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
KJH Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Kirarigaoka
Junior High
Sports Festival
Bring it this way.
To the right a little.
Announcement
Is everyone ready at the admission gate?
Can you show the families around?
Announcement
So busy!
We're almost out of time!
Announcement
Kirarigaoka Junior High School Sports Festival Exhibition
Meltic StAr Premium Concert
An-An! Sarara!
Long time no see.
Mel-chan, you know Anna-chan and Sara-chan?
Yep!
After all, Shidou Mel... is a member of Meltic StAr.
What?
I thought I recognised her from somewhere.
An-An! Sarara! I'm back! I came home!
Now Meltic StAr's a full trio again!
Don't be ridiculous.
An-An?
Meltic StAr is complete with Sara and me.
I don't have the slightest desire to associate with you again.
Sorry.
I had no idea Mel-chan was part of Meltic StAr...
What happened between them?
Kirarigaoka Junior High School Sports Festival Exhibition
Meltic StAr Premium Concert
Now it's time to start: sprinkle a little excitement
hajimeyou wakuwaku wo furimaite
I'm gonna make a channel
watashi iro no channeru
In my own colour
tsukucchaou
Throw together an outfit from my special faves
oki ni iri totteoki no koode shite
We'll wear our happy smiles
genki na sumairu
And strut our stuff
apiiru shiyou
The thought of being in the limelight gets my heart racing
ninkimono ni naritai tokimeki
Though I've always tried to keep it to myself
itsumo kakushiteita no
If you all follow me, there'll be nothing I can't do
minna no foroo ga areba muteki
So let's spread our wings
dakara habatakou
The twinkling chance we long for is sparkling
kiratto akogare kirakira kanaeru chansu da yo
Pri☆Chan's a place where dreams come to life
yume wo sakaserareru purichan
Linking hands and spreading happiness across the world
sekaijuu wo happii de tsunageyou
It'll be more fabulous than any magic
mahou yori suteki na
So come on – the show's about to start!
raibu ga hajimaru yo
We Tried Granting a Wish for a Star!
I would now like to declare the Kirarigaoka Junior High Sports Festival open.
Announcement
Akagi Anna-san will now give the athlete's oath.
Who other than I could open such a splendid event?
I swear: we shall, in our competitions, commit ourselves
to refined, beautiful and celebrity conduct.
And after this sweaty, stinking sports festival,
do recall that I have a premium concert for y–
Stop right there!
What was that?
Who said that?
Hey...
I know that voice!
Mel-chan!
Mel-Mel here issues An-An a challenge!
A challenge?
I'm joining in the sports festival!
And if I win even one more event than you,
you have to accept me as a member of Meltic StAr once more!
What?!
Mel!
Hey, that's Mel-chan, right?
She's that Meltic StAr member
who went missing all those years ago!
And now she's back!
But something's weird.
Is Mel-chan going back to Meltic StAr?
And why should I have to compete with you?
And why should  I have to compete with  you?
I'm gonna prove how good I am
and make you say you want me back in Meltic StAr!
!rAtS citleM ni kcab em tnaw uoy yas uoy ekam dna ma I doog woh evorp annog m'I
What are you talking about?
Fine with us!
Sarara!
If you can prove yourself more formidable than Anna,
you may officially return to Meltic StAr.
Anna, I know you must be feeling uneasy too.
You can vent all your worries in a match.
Isn't that more your style?
Accept it, Anna-sama!
That's right!
Prove to her that Meltic StAr's doing fine as a duo!
But a trio sounds cooler!
I wanna see Meltic StAr in its full glory again!
Very well.
If that is what you wish...
Then I shall accept this challenge!
Woo-hoo!
You won't beat ol' Mel-Mel!
Let's fight!
My red-banded comrades,
I thank you for your cooperation.
We'll make her regret ever challenging us!
Hey, everyone! Let's have a fun time with Mel-Mel!
Meltic's back!
I wanna see all three of you perform together!
Thank you! Very thank you!
She's got seriously popular vibes!
She has everyone totally fired up!
Yeah!
Just being around her is a ton of fun!
Watch out! We're gonna win it all!
Perfect victory!
Yay!
If this keeps up, it could be a complete shutout!
I'm sorry. We lost the very fir–
Wow, Mira-Mira!
You looked very, very cute when you were running!
Teach me your ways!
Uh, if that'll make you happy...
Yay! Thank you very, very much!
How dare she have so much fun even though she lost!
Grr! Next time, we'll grind them into the dirt!
We're gonna lose at this rate!
Mel-chan?
Grin.
Do you underhand?
She packed...
All the bags together!
No, it's overhead!
Wow!
She got all of them as close to the net
as she could and threw them in together.
That's a foolproof bag-tossing strategy!
It is?
Okay then! I'll give it a shot too!
The white team wins!
Grr!
Next is the teachers' costume relay.
I've gotta get ready for the next event!
Hey, Mirai-kun.
You can do it!
Go for it, Sensei!
I feel a bit guilty.
This was supposed to be a fun event for all,
but we dragged everyone into our mess.
No, that's not true at all.
Everyone's having a blast competing with Mel-chan and Anna-chan.
The two of them can rile up a crowd like no one else.
But do they really need to have a competition?
I'm sure Anna was taken aback
when Mel reappeared out of the blue.
And she's not one to change her mind easily.
Mirai-kun, would you bear with them just a little longer?
With a little help from everyone,
I know Meltic StAr will finally...
Okay!
You can count on me, Sara-chan!
I'll help out any way I can!
Thanks!
I see we can always depend on our rivals, Miracle Kiratts!
For sure!
By the way, weren't you setting up for an event?
I gotta hurry!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Giant Ball Push
Red
Team
Wins!
Red
Team
Wins!
Hup!
Grab!
Victory!
Cavalry
Battle
White
Team Wins!
Cavalry
Battle
White
Team Wins!
Cavalry
Battle
White
Team Wins!
Let's go!
Obstacle Course Race
Draw
This concludes the morning activities.
Afternoon activities will commence at 1 o'clock.
Do eat your fill, everybody.
And then...
Claim victory in the afternoon events without fail!
Anna...
Wow!
Looks yummy!
Mm-mm! The lunch Mirai's mummy made is delish!
Say, Mel-chan. What happened with you,
Anna-chan and Sara-chan?
Yeah, why do you need to have this match
instead of just joining up with them again?
An-An's mad at me.
I said I was super sorry, but she won't listen to me.
That's why.
What's Akagi Anna so mad about?
It must be because I disappeared.
3 Years Ago
We did great in Pri☆Chan again!
Yeah, it was a blast!
But we can do better still!
Someday, the whole world
shall have their eyes on Meltic StAr!
A shooting star!
You're right!
Gotta make a wish!
I hope our performances can move people's hearts more.
I hope I can eat doughnuts today, tomorrow, every day, forever and ever.
I hope the whole world doesn't get
so charmed by me that civilisation collapses.
I hope my vast talent doesn't destroy the whole world.
I hope my –
Oh no!
It's gone.
Dumb shooting stars!
They shoot and then they're all gone!
There should be a shooting star
that never falls, just for me!
Just for An-An?
If we had our own glowing celestial body, Meltic StAr would shine even brighter!
Don't you agree, Sara?
Right you are, Anna!
Meltic StAr would shine...
So I went looking for a shooting star
that would never fall.
And in the end I found a star
all for An-An.
Mel-chan.
Anna.
You're...
Mel, you idiot.
We will now begin the afternoon events.
First is the cheering competition.
The white team will be performing a flag dance.
Get ready!
Anna-chan must be mad at Mel-chan
for disappearing without saying anything.
She said she was going to look for a star.
But how are you even supposed to do that?
I don't get it.
I wonder if we can help her out somehow.
Maybe we can create a chance for them
to talk it out during the event somehow?
Okay.
Yay!
Hooray!
Yippee!
Anna.
The next event will be ours!
Anna!
Behold the red of passion.
And the red of the "aka" in Akagi Anna!
Silence
W-Well, that performance certainly had character!
Just a reminder: the cheering competition
does not have a winner!
For Heaven's sake!
And after we trounced them so thoroughly!
You really think so?
Red Team!
White Team!
Kirarigaoka Junior High School Sports Festival Exhibition
Meltic StAr Premium Concert
Tie!
It's time for the final event:
a relay event featuring both teams'
hand-picked top members!
We shall claim victory in this relay, you see!
Stop being stubborn, Anna.
Just hear Mel out.
I refuse!
The red team's anchor is Anna-chan,
just like we thought.
Kirarigaoka Junior High School Sports Festival Exhibition
Meltic StAr Premium Concert
I've discussed it with Sara-chan.
Then all that's left is...
Yeah.
Mel!
What's up?
This is the last round.
Let's make sure your feelings get across to Anna-chan!
Yep – we'll send across your sparkling feelings!
Sparkling?
Sparkling...
On your marks...
Get set...
Mel's the one who up and disappeared.
Does she expect me to welcome her back with open arms?
Not while I have pride in this body!
My, so you're the anchor.
That's a pity.
Our second runner put us in quite the lead.
And with Sara, not even Mel could –
An-An!
She has overtaken Sara?
What? Why is Mel in the red team?
We had Sara-chan and Mel-chan swap teams.
Mel-chan has something she wants to give you!
Something to give me?
An-An!
I will not accept it.
But you'll lose.
Hey.
Remember this?
What might this be?
A star for you!
So, um, after a shooting star burns out,
it leaves debris in the ground!
She had them sent all the way from the North Pole.
This won't disappear!
You really don't comprehend, do you?
Your wish won't count unless it's in the sky.
In the sky?
So it can't be a shooting star just for us.
That said, I suppose I will take one.
That's why.
I went to look for a shooting star that'd never fall.
For all this time.
And I found one!
Surely you didn't... go to the US for that alone?
Anna! Run!
Mel went on a journey – and returned – all for you!
Now's the time for Meltic StAr
to start moving forward again!
Mirai-kun!
You got it!
Do you get it now?
Mel-chan wanted to find a star
just for you more than anything!
That's why she left... and why she couldn't come back!
Kirarigaoka Junior High School Sports Festival Exhibition
Meltic StAr Premium Concert
All right!
They're together again!
Sara! Akagi Anna!
The stage is yours!
Show us what kinda vibes Meltic StAr can dish out they're at their best!
Show us! Show us!
Very well, then.
Do you remember the song we did as a trio?
You betcha!
I didn't forget the tiniest bit of it!
Then let us go!
Kirarigaoka Junior High School Sports Festival Exhibition
Meltic StAr Premium Concert
It's time...
For Meltic StAr to put on a show!
Dance "gave it a try app": set!
PriTicket: swipe!
My unbeatable and perfect Pri☆Chan's live on the air!
Check it out!
It's a super cool Mel-Mel outfit!
You may gaze upon my lovely raiment!
Sharp!
Here it is: my impeccably cool outfit!
We're Meltic StAr.
Today's outfit is the Punk Cat Ensemble.
Mel's wearing it in a brand-new colour.
Now Meltic StAr's concert...
Is starting!
You see!
When you start yearning for radiance
kagayaki wa akogareta shunkan
It seems so far away
doushite ka tookunacchau kedo
(Longing for, longing for, longing for – chu chu la!)
(longing for longing for longing for chu chu la)
(Longing for, longing for, longing for that star)
(longing for longing for longing for star)
The glimmer passing right by
me no mae wo toorisugita shining
Whips up a solar flare in my heart
kizuitara okotteru my big bang
(Longing for, longing for, longing for that star)
(longing for longing for longing for star)
And it's dancing, sparkling in the sky
ima kiratto sora ni odoru
(Like a twinkling star)
(hoshi mitai ni)
This miracle eclipses all else in our minds
hitosuji no kiseki sagase
(This song's taking off!)
(up and shooting song)
(This dance is taking off!)
(up and shooting dance)
(This show's leaving the Earth!)
(up and shooting this stage)
This cometic silhouette showers us with happiness
cometic shiruetto furase shiawase
As we dance in the hall of all the cosmos
uchuu datte dansuhooru
Mixing our lovely, cool and poppy styles together
lovely coolish poppu wo mazekoze
One, two, and...
I gave it a try!
We'll see the dawn of a new world
atarashii sekai
This cometic silhouette showers you with happiness
cometic shiruetto furase shiawase
Let's party!
All the cosmos is a hall for us to dance
uchuu datte dansuhooru
A shooting star that never falls!
With the brilliance of this one unique star
onriiwan na hoshi wo kirameki
Anna!
Mel!
Sarara!
I like it!
We'll see a brand new world
atarashii sekai
Sweet Sweet Dancing Queen!
This cometic silhouette holds the thread of all your dreams
cometic shiruetto souzou no shippo wa
Stretching forth into infinity
mugendai ni nobiteku yo
And you raise your eyes to see
miageta kimi no hitomi ni
This Meltic StAr for you!
todoku meltic star
This Meltic StAr shines true!
hikaru meltic star
I brought this meteorite from the North Pole, didja know?
Fr-From the North Pole?
A lot of meteorites that don't burn up
in the Earth's atmosphere ends up at the North Pole.
I see.
But stars that fall aren't shooting stars anymore.
So that's why I wanted to find a shooting star.
One that wouldn't fall, just like you said.
That's what took me to the ol' US of A!
I went there and studied up a lot.
In order to find a shooting star that'd never fall, I joined NASA too.
NASA?
Who's nursing?
The US national space agency.
But even if you do study, not just anyone can get in.
That's where I found what I was looking for!
I found a shooting star that'll never fall – for you, An-An!
When'd it get so big?
I could barely see it a moment ago!
It's a comet.
A star that keeps circling the globe.
So this is the star you found.
A shooting star that never falls.
Yep!
Mel-Mel here was the first in the world to discover it!
So I got to name it!
Name it?
Yep! And I called it...
Meltic StAr!
A shooting star that never falls.
A great comet that keeps shining.
It's like an unchanging bond, linking us together!
Aren't you happy, An-An?
I mean...
You're crying.
How could I not be happy?
Mel!
Oh, Mel!
We've been waiting for you this whole time.
Welcome back, Mel!
I'm home!
I'm so glad!
Hooray for Meltic StAr!
A great comet shining forever in the night sky.
For all three of them!
This is a brand-new sparkling start for Meltic StAr!
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Pri☆Chan!
chanchan puu chanchan puu purichan
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, time to begin!
chanchan puu chanchan puu hajimaru
Sending max excitement through the screen
sukurin goshi dokidoki makkusu
Shining like crazy! It's like a jewel!
kirameki ippai houseki mitai
Laughter and tears and happiness and everything else
warai naki yorokobi nandemo
This magic sends it all to you!
tsutaeteikeru mahou da yo
Come on, don't you want to try it too?
hora kimi mo mezashitai desho
Com on, then, I'll show you!
sore nara oshiete ageru ne
Just put a bit of courage in your pocket
yuuki chotto poochi ni iretara
Here we go, time for Pri☆Chan!
ima sugu purichan
No rivals here
raibaru nante inai
We're dreamers, one and all
yume miru hito wa minna
It's so cute! I love it a bunch!
kawaii ne meccha suki
Let's be friends!
let's be friends
On this channel of dreams, we can all be
yume e no channeru de dare mo ga minna
Gleaming, gleaming, glee
pikkan pikkan pii
Yes, you and me as well
ima sugu hora kimi mo boku mo
Let's be cute kitty idols
nyawa aidoru desu
Give it a tap, give it a swipe
pikon tappu tappu chotto suwaipu
Gleaming, gleaming, glee
pikkan pikkan pii
And send all your love out
okki na ai sekaijuu ni
Across the whole world
todokete ne
All together!
issho ni
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Pri☆Chan!
chanchan puu chanchan puu purichan
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan☆Pri? Wait, that's wrong!
chanchan puu chanchan puu chanpuri chigau
Chan-Chan-Pu, Chan-Chan-Pu, Pri☆Chan!
chanchan puu chanchan puu purichan
Check it out! It's time to begin!
mite mite hajimaru
Next Time
Good morning! Hello-hello! It's Mel-Mel!
Nice to meet you, everyone!
And look, you've got wrapped up in a fine mess already!
Yes!
I found a strange stranger lying flat on the street!
He's got crazy amnesia
and doesn't remember who he is at all!
Take him to the police then.
No! No!
This is Mel-Mel's time to shine!
Come again?
Next time, Mel Tried Becoming a Detective!
Join hands and expand our follower world!
Mel Tried Becoming a Detective!
Our fabulous show's live on the air!
You see!